[{"id":"4687","question":"<p>I don&rsquo;t think the law will interfere with us as we are just trying to <strong>turn an honest penny.<\/strong><\/p>\r\n","option1":"make a legitimate","option2":"make a good living","option3":"have dealings in white money","option4":"become more honest  ","option5":"None of these ","correct_option":"make a good living","qa_date":"2015-11-19 20:58:12","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p>make a legitimate living.&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"4679","question":"<p>Teachers of various schools (1)\/met to discuss about (2) how to improve the standard of English. (3)\/ No error. (4).<\/p>\r\n","option1":"1","option2":"2","option3":"3","option4":"4","option5":"5","correct_option":"2","qa_date":"2015-11-19 20:49:38","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p>The error lies in part (2) of the sentence. The preposition &lsquo;about&rsquo; has superfluously been used here.<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p style=\"margin-left:72.0pt\">For example:<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p style=\"margin-left:72.0pt\">We discussed when to go\/when we should go.<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"4684","question":"<p>In sprit of the immense pressure exerted by the militants, the Government has decided not to <strong>give in.<\/strong><\/p>\r\n","option1":"accede","option2":"yield","option3":"oblige","option4":"conform","option5":"None of these","correct_option":"yield","qa_date":"2015-11-19 20:58:12","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p>yield&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"4686","question":"<p>We want to keep gift as a surprise for mother but by sister <strong>gave the game away.<\/strong><\/p>\r\n","option1":"loss the game","option2":"gave out the secret","option3":"played badly","option4":"withdraw from the game","option5":"None of these","correct_option":"gave out the secret","qa_date":"2015-11-19 20:58:12","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p>gave out the secret<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"4685","question":"<p>The young and old sat <strong>cheek by jowl <\/strong>in the large audience.<\/p>\r\n","option1":"very near","option2":"very far","option3":"tongue tied","option4":"irritated","option5":"None of these","correct_option":"very near","qa_date":"2015-11-19 20:58:12","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p>very near<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"4681","question":"<p>The two first of arrive (1)\/ were the lucky recipients (2)\/ of a surprise gift. (3)\/ No error (4)<\/p>\r\n","option1":"1","option2":"2","option3":"3","option4":"4","option5":"5","correct_option":"1","qa_date":"2015-11-19 20:49:38","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p>&ldquo;The two first to arrive&rdquo; should be replaced with &lsquo;the first two of arrive&rsquo; to make a correct sense of the sentences.&nbsp;<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"4683","question":"<p>The watchdogs were asleep when the bulls <strong>ran riot.<\/strong><\/p>\r\n","option1":"behaved cleverly ","option2":"acted without restraint ","option3":"wandered aimlessly.","option4":"wad the best of time.","option5":"None of these","correct_option":"acted without restraint ","qa_date":"2015-11-19 20:58:12","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p>acted without restraint<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"4676","question":"<p>Scarcely had (1)\/ I arrived than (2)\/ the train left. (3)\/ No error. (4).<\/p>\r\n","option1":"1","option2":"2","option3":"3","option4":"4","option5":"5","correct_option":"2","qa_date":"2015-11-19 20:44:35","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p style=\"margin-left:72.0pt\">Scarcely should be followed by <strong>when<\/strong> and not by <strong>than.<\/strong><\/p>\r\n\r\n<p style=\"margin-left:72.0pt\">For example:<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p style=\"margin-left:72.0pt\">Scarcely had he gone, when(not than) a policeman knocked at the door.<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p style=\"margin-left:72.0pt\">Hence, <strong>than<\/strong> should be replaced by <strong>when.<\/strong><\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"4680","question":"<p>His tradition-bound attitude (1)\/ had to be constant source of dissatisfaction (2)\/ among the young members of the family (3)\/No error. (4).<\/p>\r\n","option1":"1","option2":"2","option3":"3","option4":"4","option5":"5","correct_option":"4","qa_date":"2015-11-19 20:49:38","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p>No error<\/p>\r\n"},{"id":"4678","question":"<p>The reason why (1)\/ he was rejected (2) was because he was too young. (3)\/ No error. (4).<\/p>\r\n","option1":"1","option2":"2","option3":"3","option4":"4","option5":"5","correct_option":"3","qa_date":"2015-11-19 20:49:38","section_description":"","max_marks":"1","answer":"<p>After such opening as <strong>The reason is, the reason why<\/strong>, the clause, containing the reason must being with &lsquo;because&rsquo; but with &lsquo;that&rsquo;.<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p style=\"margin-left:72.0pt\">For example:<\/p>\r\n\r\n<p style=\"margin-left:72.0pt\">The reason why he is absent is that he is ill. Hence <strong>because <\/strong>should be replaced with <strong>that.<\/strong><\/p>\r\n"}]